class Calc {
  Calc({
    required this.question,
    required this.answer,
  });

  final String question;
  final String answer;
}

List<Calc> calcQuestions = [
  Calc(question: '25 × 3 - 5 = ?', answer: '70'),
  Calc(question: '60 ÷ 2 + 10 = ?', answer: '40'),
  Calc(question: '(30 + 20) × 2 = ?', answer: '100'),
  Calc(question: '150 ÷ 3 + 5 = ?', answer: '55'),
  Calc(question: '40 × 2 - 3 = ?', answer: '77'),
  Calc(question: '(12 × 6) + 5 = ?', answer: '77'),
  Calc(question: '200 ÷ 4 + 20 = ?', answer: '70'),
  Calc(question: '35 × 2 - 10 = ?', answer: '60'),
  Calc(question: '80 + 12 × 3 = ?', answer: '116'),
  Calc(question: '(10 + 5) × 6 = ?', answer: '90'),
  Calc(question: '50 × 2 - 10 = ?', answer: '90'),
  Calc(question: '(20 + 30) × 2 = ?', answer: '100'),
  Calc(question: '120 ÷ 4 + 20 = ?', answer: '50'),
  Calc(question: '10 × 8 - 4 = ?', answer: '76'),
  Calc(question: '(15 × 4) + 10 = ?', answer: '70'),
  Calc(question: '40 × 3 - 25 = ?', answer: '95'),
  Calc(question: '150 ÷ 5 + 10 = ?', answer: '40'),
  Calc(question: '80 + 10 × 3 = ?', answer: '110'),
  Calc(question: '25 × 5 - 20 = ?', answer: '105'),
  Calc(question: '(45 × 2) - 5 = ?', answer: '85'),
];
